Guide to the Sara and Gerald Murphy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Honoria Murphy Donnelly Papers, 1925-2003; Series VII; 5.84 linear feet (15 boxes)
  - Printed Materials
    - Ephemera from Exhibitions of Gerald Murphy's Artwork
      - The Dallas Museum of Art, "An American Painter in Paris: Gerald Murphy," photographs, and other ephemera, 1978, 1986, 1999 (Box 107, Folder 1107-1114)
      - Federal Reserve System, " Gerald Murphy: Toward an Understanding of His Art and Inspiration", 1983 (Box 108, Folder 1115)
      - Hirschl & Adler Galleries, "Modern Times: 1907-1956", 1986 (Box 108, Folder 1116)
      - The Phillips Collection, "Americans in Paris", 1996 (Box 108, Folder 1117-1121)
      - Museum of Modern Art, "Objects of Desire", 1994 (Box 108, Folder 1122-1123)
      - Royal Academy of Arts, "American Art in the 20th Century", 1993-1994 (Box 108, Folder 1124)
      - Reproductions of Gerald Murphy's artwork in various publications, 1993-2004 (Box 108, Folder 1125-1126)
      - Reproductions of Gerald Murphy's artwork in various publications, 1993-2004 (Box 109, Folder 1127-1131)
    - Writings Inspired by the Murphys
      - "Sara & Gerald" miniseries from American Playhouse, proposal, script, and reviews, 1989 (Box 109, Folder 1132-1135)
        Dramatization of Honoria Donnelly's memoir
      - Vaill, Amanda, Everybody Was So Young, reviews, 1998 (Box 109, Folder 1136-1137)
      - Williams, Tennessee, "Clothes for a Summer Hotel," program and reviews, 1979-1980 (Box 109, Folder 1138)
    - Subject Files
      - Fanny Brennan, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 1139)
      - Beatrice Ashley Chanler, 1946 (Box 110, Folder 1140)
      - Honoria Donnelly, circa 1940 (Box 110, Folder 1141)
      - John Dos Passos, 1937-1964, undated (Box 110, Folder 1142)
      - F. Scott and Zelda Fitzgerald, 1955-1996 (Box 110, Folder 1143-1148)
        Includes notes by Gerald Murphy
      - Ernest Hemingway, 1951-1981 (Box 110, Folder 1149-1150)
      - Fernand Léger, 1991-1998 (Box 110, Folder 1151-1152)
        Includes photocopies of postcards sent by Léger to the Murphy family and photocopies of Léger's sketchbook from his sailing trip with the Murphys in 1934
      - Archibald MacLeish, 1979-1982 (Box 110, Folder 1153)
      - Dorothy Parker, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 1154)
      - Pablo Picasso, 1964-1980 (Box 110, Folder 1155)
      - Cole Porter, 1990-2003 (Box 111, Folder 1156-1157)
      - Mark Cross Company, 1990-1995, undated (Box 111, Folder 1158-1160)
      - Franklin Delano and Eleanor Roosevelt, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 1161)
      - Berton Roueché, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 1162)
      - Les Six, 1952-1955 (Box 111, Folder 1163)
      - Frank Wiborg, 1930 (Box 111, Folder 1164-1165)
      - Mary Hoyt Wiborg, 1927, undated (Box 111, Folder 1166)
      - Villa America, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 1167-1168)
      - "Within the Quota", 1970-1997 (Box 111, Folder 1169-1170)
      - "Within the Quota", 1970-1997 (Box 112, Folder 1171-1172)
      - Advertisement with catch phrase "Living Well is the Best Revenge", 1980 (Box 112, Folder 1173)
      - Stamp and postcard collection, 1939-1950, undated (Box 112, Folder 1174-1175)
    - Other Printed Material
      - Important Impressionist and Modern Paintings and Sculptures (New York: Sotheby Parke Bernet, Inc.), 1976 (Box 112, Folder 1176)
        Auction catalogue includes "Composition A 1 Profil" given by Fernand Léger to Sara and Gerald
- Patrick Francis & Anna Elizabeth Ryan Murphy Papers, 1863-1931; Series VIII; 3.55 linear feet (9 boxes)
  The series is organized into three subseries: Notebooks, Other Papers, and Papers relating to Frederic and Noël Haskins Murphy.
  Biographical/Historical note
  Patrick Francis Murphy (1858-1931)
  Patrick Francis Murphy was one of thirteen children born in Boston on July 25th, 1858 to Irish immigrants. After attending Boston Latin School, Murphy became a salesman for Mark W. Cross, a leather goods company specializing in saddles and harnesses. Murphy bought the company following Cross's death and continued to expand its production of luxury personal leather goods (a successful direction that Murphy had suggested that Cross pursue). Murphy served as a member of the Massachusetts Legislature from roughly 1887 to 1889. Murphy married Anna Elizabeth Ryan, also of Boston, and the couple had three children: Frederic T. Murphy, Gerald Cleary Murphy, and Esther Murphy. In 1891 Murphy moved his family and business to New York City where his business thrived and where he became popular as an after-dinner speaker. Murphy died from pneumonia in New York in 1931.
  Frederic Timothy Murphy (1885-1924) and Noël Haskins (1895-1982)
  Frederic T. Murphy was the eldest child of Patrick Francis and Anna Ryan Murphy. He attended Hotchkiss and Yale University (1908). After graduation Murphy worked for the Mark Cross Company as treasurer, general manager, and then secretary. In 1917 Murphy enrolled as a Private in the Sixth Field Artillery at Fort Myers and was sent to France in December to serve with the army and then the Tank Corps. Murphy was awarded the Croix de Guerre (1918), the Cross of the Legion of Honor (1923), and the Conspicuous Service Medal (1923). In 1920 Murphy and Noël Haskins married in New York. The couple lived in London and then settled permanently in France. Murphy died in Paris, France on May 23rd, 1924 from war-related wounds.
  Noël Haskins, one of two daughters of Charles Waldo and Henrietta Havemeyer Haskins, was born on December 25, 1895. As a young woman Haskins trained to be a singer and was involved in theatre, performing with the Washington Square Players. Haskins continued to take voice lessons while living in Europe after her marriage. Following Murphy's death in 1924, Haskins moved permanently to Orgeval, France, where she entertained a number of guests including her lover Janet Flanner and sister-in-law Esther Murphy. During World War II she served with the Comité Américain de Secours Civil and was sent by the Nazis to an internment camp in Vittel. Haskins died in France in 1982.
  Description of the Papers
  The series largely documents Gerald Murphy's father, Patrick Francis Murphy, and brother, Frederic Murphy, and consists of notebooks, correspondence, and other papers. Patrick Murphy's notebooks date from 1890 to 1931 (the year of his death) and contain quotes from newspapers and various witticisms, which were likely later used in his popular after-dinner speeches. The Other Papers subseries also concerns Patrick Murphy's role as a lecturer and includes drafts for his talks and an assortment of related newspaper clippings. Among Patrick Murphy's roles as President of the Mark Cross Company was marketing; this responsibility is represented in various notes and newspaper clippings that contain copy for advertisements (for the most part consisting of epigrams), printed advertisements, and directions for window displays.
  The life of Frederic Murphy, particularly between 1918 and 1924, is traced in the correspondence he sent to his parents as well as a scrapbook created by his mother Anna Murphy. The material also relates to Frederic Murphy's wife, Noël Haskins, although to a lesser degree. The correspondence and scrapbooks cover the period when Frederic Murphy trained and then fought with the Tank Corps in France during World War I. In his correspondence Frederic Murphy discusses his experiences as a soldier, his health, family members (including Gerald's painting projects), and postwar life in France. Although Frederic Murphy died in 1924 the Papers include photographs of Noël Haskins Murphy from various periods, including her service with the Comité Américain de Secours Civil in France (in 1938) and at her home in Orgeval, France. Anna Murphy's scrapbook provides details about her son's military career, including letters, newspaper clippings, and photographs.
  - Notebooks
    - Notebook, 1890 (Box 113, Folder 1177)
    - Notebooks "1" - "2", "4" - "5", "7"- "9", circa 1909-1919, undated (Box 113, Folder 1178-1184)
    - Notebooks "10" - "16", circa 1919-1931 (Box 114, Folder 1185-1195)
    - Notebooks "17" - "25", circa 1917-1925 (Box 115, Folder 1196-1205)
    - Notebooks "26" - "27" and unnumbered, 1923-1931 (Box 116, Folder 1206-1218)
    - Notebook containing clippings "Memory Lessons" by R.F. Foster from the Globe, 1908 (Box 117, Folder 1219)
    - Blank notebooks, undated (Box 117, Folder 1220-1223)
    - Small "jotter" notebooks, undated (Box 117, Folder 1224-1226)
    - Small "jotter" notebooks, undated (Box 118, Folder 1227-1233)
    - Small "jotter" notebooks, undated (Box 119, Folder 1234)
    - Notebook with clipping "Boston Man Shines as Wit in New York" from the Boston American, 1904 December 21 (Box 119, Folder 1235)
  - Other Papers
    - Leather folio and various notes, clippings, and printed material, 1910-1931 (Box 119, Folder 1236-1241)
      Includes notes on readings, notes of various witticisms, music lyrics, and printed material on golf
    - Clippings and notes regarding marketing for the Mark Cross Company, 1913-1928, undated (Box 119, Folder 1242-1246)
      Includes binder, drafts and printed versions of advertisements, notes on window displays
    - Clippings and notes regarding marketing for the Mark Cross Company, 1913-1928, undated (Box 120, Folder 1247-1249)
    - Drafts of speeches, 1910-1930, undated (Box 120, Folder 1250-1251)
      Includes speeches for the Credit Men's Association, Manhattan Club, and titled "St. Nicholos," "Dr. Parkhurst," "Buffalo," "HS 1910," "Sherriff's Jury 1914," "George Cohan," "Luncheon to O'Brien," "Lamb's Gambol," "Boston," and "Greenhorn"
    - Clipping "Wit and Humor of New York's Famous After-Dinner Speaker" tribute to Patrick F. Murphy, 1931 (Box 120, Folder 1252)
    - Clipping from The Massachusetts Spy, 1863 January 28
  - Papers relating to Frederic and Noël Haskins Murphy
    - Memorial card for Henrietta Havemeyer (Noël Haskins' grandmother), 1888 (Box 121, Folder 1253)
    - Correspondence sent from Frederic Murphy to his family, 1917-1924, undated (Box 121, Folder 1254-1259)
      Includes some letters from Noël Haskins Murphy, clippings, and other ephemera
    - Scrapbook with clippings, letters, and photographs relating to Frederic Murphy created by Anna Murphy, 1915-1924 (Box 121, Folder 1260)
    - Loose clippings and photographs removed from scrapbook, 1915-1924 (Box 121, Folder 1261-1262)
      Includes photographs of Frederic Murphy in Santa Barbara, California in 1915 and his snapshots of Hotel Potter and the filming of a movie (photograph annotated "Mrs. Graham's"); Murphy wearing a gas mask in 1918, with soldiers in France following WWI (at the Hermitage in Coye), and various shots of Europe.
    - Frederic Murphy's visa for Haiti, 1919 (Box 121, Folder 1263)
- Wiborg Family Papers, 1854-1930; Series IX; 8.34 linear feet ( 20 boxes)
  The series is organized into three subseries: Frank Wiborg Diaries, Other Papers, and Mary Hoyt Wiborg Papers.
  Frank Bestow Wiborg (1855-1930)
  Frank Wiborg, Sara Murphy's father, was born to Henry Paulinus Wiborg (1821-1867) and Susan Isidora Bestow (1832-1876) in 1855 in Cleveland, Ohio. Frank and his younger brother Harry left Cleveland for Cincinnati following the death of their father and their mother's remarriage. While in Cincinnati Wiborg attended the Chickering Institute, graduating in 1874, and began his career as a businessman. After various positions, including a stint with the Remington Sewing Machine Company, Frank Wiborg began working for Levi Addison Ault to produce printing inks. In 1878 the men entered into a formal partnership creating the Ault & Wiborg Company. Wiborg and Adeline Moulton Sherman were married in 1882, an event which Wiborg describes in his diary. Adeline was the daughter of Hoyt Sherman and the niece of William Tecumseh Sherman and Ohio Senator John Sherman.
  The success of the Ault & Wiborg Company prompted its expansion to New York (461 Eighth Avenue) as well as Canada, Europe, South America, and China. Wiborg's business interests led to his family's relocation to Germany for a period in 1898, where the Wiborgs socialized with Kaiser Wilhelm II and his family. Frank Wiborg's travels through South America on behalf of his company resulted in his publication A Commercial Traveler in South America (New York: McClure, Phillips & Co, 1905).
  The Wiborgs maintained homes in Cincinnati, New York City, and Long Island ("The Dunes"). The Wiborg family was involved in a number of social and civic organizations, and in his semi-retirement Frank Wiborg became engaged in politics. In 1907-1908 Wiborg served as secretary of the National Council of Commerce, a body created by and reporting to the Secretary of Commerce and Labor during the Theodore Roosevelt administration. President Taft appointed Wiborg Assistant Secretary of Commerce and Labor in 1909. Wiborg accompanied General Nelson Appleton Miles, who was married to one of Adeline Sherman's cousins, on several trips such as an excursion to the American Southwest in 1896 and a trip around the world in 1902 (Wiborg later used his diaries from this trip to produce The Travels of an Unofficial Attaché ).
  Although retired, Wiborg continued to be engaged in his business, publishing Printing Ink: A History with a Treatise on Modern Methods of Manufacture and Use in 1926 (Wiborg was working on a second volume of the treatise at the time of his death). In 1928 the Ault & Wiborg Company merged with International Printing Inc. Wiborg died of pneumonia at his home, 756 Park Avenue, New York City, in 1930.
  The series contains documents relating to Frank Wiborg, Adeline Moulton Sherman Wiborg ("Addie"), and Mary Hoyt Wiborg ("Hoytie").
  Frank Wiborg was a dedicated diarist whose journals cover his daily life from ages eighteen to fifty-nine (1873-1914) and trace his education and evolution into a prominent businessman. In his diaries Frank Wiborg records his observations of his family, his work life, and his involvement in society and politics. Wiborg chronicles his experiences as a student at the Chickering Institute and his early employment. Wiborg notes a number of important moments in his life, including his graduation, marriage to Adeline Sherman, the births of his three daughters, his involvement in politics, and his travels with General Nelson Appleton Miles.
  Wiborg describes the family's everyday life, recording theatre attended and books read, as well as their lifestyle while living in Cincinnati, New York City, East Hampton, and Germany, and their travels (for example, in Europe and India). The diaries represent, through Frank Wiborg's eyes, the lives of his wife and daughters, and include various newspaper clippings recounting their activities and artwork given to him by his daughters. Clippings from a later period (1927-1930) can be found in Wiborg's scrapbook. The diaries contain Frank Wiborg's impressions of Sara Wiborg's life from birth until just before her marriage to Gerald Murphy and thus provide rich insight into her childhood and adolescence. Various ephemera are tucked into the pages of the diaries, including photographs, newspaper clippings, calling cards, invitations, ticket stubs, letters, and postcards.
  The Ault & Wiborg Company is represented in Frank Wiborg's diaries, as well as in the Other Papers subseries, which includes two copies of the company's posters (one of which was created by Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec), and Wiborg's book Printing Ink: A History with a Treatise on Modern Methods of Manufacture and Use. For example, the diaries chronicle the development of the partnership between Wiborg and his partner Levi Addison Ault, the company's incorporation (1891), subsequent expansions, and day-to-day struggles, such as preventing the flammable materials used to produce printing inks from igniting.
  The Other Papers subseries also includes Adeline Sherman Wiborg's recipe book dating from the year of her marriage. Papers of Susan Isidora Bestow Wiborg, Frank Wiborg's mother, can be found in her diary (written in the year her husband died), her Bible, and a letter from a cousin. Mary Hoyt Wiborg's scrapbook, "1904 Automobile Trip Along the Loire," chronicles the Wiborg family's travels through France as well as brief notes regarding the family's stops in London and Berlin.
  - Frank Wiborg Diaries
    - Diary, 1873 (Box 122, Folder 1264)
    - Diary, 1874 (Box 122, Folder 1265)
    - Diary, 1875 (Box 122, Folder 1266-1267)
    - Diary, 1876 (Box 122, Folder 1268-1269)
    - Diary, 1877 (Box 122, Folder 1270-1271)
    - Diary, 1878 (Box 123, Folder 1272-1273)
    - Diary, 1879 (Box 123, Folder 1274-1275)
    - Diary, 1880 (Box 123, Folder 1276-1277)
    - Diary, 1881 (Box 123, Folder 1278-1279)
    - Diary, 1882 (Box 124, Folder 1280-1281)
    - Diary, 1883 (Box 124, Folder 1282)
    - Diary, 1884 (Box 124, Folder 1283-1284)
    - Diary, 1885 (Box 124, Folder 1285)
    - Diary, 1886 (Box 124, Folder 1286)
    - Diary, 1887 (Box 125, Folder 1287-1288)
    - Diary, 1888 (Box 125, Folder 1289-1290)
    - Diary, 1889 (Box 125, Folder 1291-1292)
    - Diary, 1890 (Box 125, Folder 1293-1294)
    - Diary, 1891 (Box 126, Folder 1295-1297)
    - Diary, 1892 (Box 126, Folder 1298-1300)
    - Diary, 1893 (Box 126, Folder 1301-1303)
    - Diary, 1894 (Box 127, Folder 1304-1306)
    - Diary, 1895 (Box 127, Folder 1307-1310)
    - Diary, 1896 (Box 128, Folder 1311-1313)
    - Diary, 1897 (Box 128, Folder 1314-1318)
    - Diary, 1898 (Box 129, Folder 1319-1322)
    - Diary, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 1323-1325)
    - Diary, 1900 (Box 130, Folder 1326-1328)
    - Diary, 1901 (Box 131, Folder 1329-1331)
    - Diary, 1902 (Box 131, Folder 1332-1335)
    - Diary, 1903 (Box 132, Folder 1336-1340)
    - Diary, 1904 (Box 133, Folder 1341-1344)
    - Diary, 1905 (Box 134, Folder 1345-1348)
    - Diary, 1906 (Box 135, Folder 1349-1352)
    - Diary, 1907 (Box 135, Folder 1353)
    - Diary, 1907 (Box 136, Folder 1354-1356)
    - Diary, 1908 (Box 136, Folder 1357-1362)
    - Diary, 1909 (Box 137, Folder 1363-1366)
    - Diary, 1910 (Box 137, Folder 1367-1369)
    - Diary, 1911-1912 (Box 138, Folder 1370-1375)
    - Diary, 1912 (Box 138, Folder 1376)
    - Diary, 1912 (Box 139, Folder 1377-1378)
    - Diary, 1913 (Box 139, Folder 1379-1381)
    - Diary, 1913-1914 (Box 139, Folder 1382-1386)
  - Other Papers
    - Letter to Susan Isidora Bestow Wiborg from a cousin, 1863 July 24 (Box 140, Folder 1387)
    - Bible belonging to Susan Isidora Bestow Wiborg, 1854 (Box 140, Folder 1388)
    - Diary of Susan Isidora Bestow Wiborg, 1867 (Box 140, Folder 1389)
    - Recipe book belonging to "Addie M. Sherman" (Adeline Moulton Sherman Wiborg ), 1882 (Box 140, Folder 1390)
    - Ault & Wiborg Co. poster with image of world, undated (Box 140, Folder 1391)
    - Photograph of Ault & Wiborg Co. poster by Toulouse-Lautrec, undated (Box 140, Folder 1392)
    - The Travels of an Unofficial Attaché by Frank Wiborg (privately printed), 1904 (Box 141, Folder 1393)
    - Printing Ink: A History with a Treatise on Modern Methods of Manufacture and Use by Frank Wiborg (New York and London: Harper & Brothers), 1926 (Box 141, Folder 1394)
    - Postcards sent by Frank Wiborg to his brother Harry Wiborg, 1923, 1926 (Box 141, Folder 1395)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings collected by Frank Wiborg, 1927-1930
  - Mary Hoyt Wiborg Papers
    - Scrapbook of "1904 Automobile Trip Along the Loire", 1904-1905 (Box 141, Folder 1396)
- Additions Since 2011, 1880s-2005; Series X; 5.09; (20 boxes) + 1 art
  Organized into five subseries: Personal Papers, Photographs, Artwork, Objects, and Audiovisual Material.
  Box 229 (audiovisual material): ‡a Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 230 (audiovisual material) ‡a Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Personal Papers
    - Articles, undated; 2 (Box 210)
    - Autogaph manuscript letter, signed, from May Brawley Hill to Mr. Donnelly, 2005 December 9 (Box 210)
    - Caption sheets, undated (Box 210)
    - "Cheer Hall" guest book, 1950-1951 (Box 210)
    - "Gay Mad Party" notes, autograph manuscript, 1920s (Box 210)
    - Inventories, undated (Box 210)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 210)
    - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 210)
    - "REM," poem, typescript (photocopy), undated (Box 210)
    - Sara Murphy's birthday book, undated (Box 210)
    - Stamp booklet, undated (Box 210)
    - "Villa America," postcards, undated (Box 211)
  - Photographs
    - "Boat Desk Portrait", 1922-1923, undated (Box 212)
    - "Engine Room (aka Pressure)", undated (Box 212)
    - Photographs of Hemingway and others, 1920s, undated; 8 (Box 212)
    - "Portrait of Leger", undated (Box 212)
    - Unlabeled photographs of Murphy family and others, mounted, undated; 4 (Box 213)
    - Unlabeled photographs of Murphy family and others, mounted, undated; 4 (Box 214)
    - Photographs of Murphy family, 1920s, undated; 3 (Box 214)
    - Photograph album, circa 1880s-1910 (Box 215)
    - Photograph album of "The Grand Tour, Sara W. Murphy w/ Sisters and Mother Motoring thru Europe... Book II", 1904, undated (Box 216)
    - Photographs of Murphy family members by Man Ray and Lee Miller, undated; 9 (Box 217)
    - Photographs of Murphy family members by Man Ray and Lee Miller, undated; 6 (Box 218)
    - Photograph of Wiborg sisters, framed, undated (Box 219 (Art))
    - Original and copy negatives, undated; 10 (Box 220)
      Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Artwork
    - Drawings by Fernard Léger, undated (Box 221)
    - Drawing of Fernard Léger by Patrick Murphy, undated (Box 221)
    - Crayon Still Life attributed to Gerald Murphy, undated (Box 221)
    - "Montrouge" by L. S. [Survass?], 1924 (Box 221)
    - Watercolor by Fernard Léger, undated (Box 221)
    - Drawing by L. Survass, 1929 (Box 221)
    - Unidentified work, undated (Box 221)
    - Facsimile of "Turbines" by Gerald Murphy, mounted on board, undated (Box 222)
    - Facsimile of portrait by Gerald Murply, mounted on board, undated (Box 222)
    - Watercolor of Murphy children by Fernard Léger, framed, undated (Box 223)
    - Watercolor of Sara Murphy by Fernard Léger, framed, 1934 (Box 224)
    - Watercolor of Gerald Murphy by Fernard Léger, 1934 (Box 225)
  - Objects
    - Gloves and glove hanger, undated (Box 226)
    - Neck ties, undated (Box 227)
    - Scissors, undated (Box 227)
    - Vest by Mark Cross, undated (Box 228 (Oversize))
    - Waistbands, undated (Box 228 (Oversize))
  - Audiovisual Material
    - "Hemingway Home Movies", camera rolls 1-3 (videocassette), 1999 August 10; 1 (Box 229, Item barcode 39002109973991)
    - "Grandmother, Mother & Daughter," I. J. Fox singing (16" album), undated (Box 230 (Art))
- Oversize and Rolled Storage, 5.88 linear feet (30 boxes)
  - Oversize
    - Brown leather scrapbook with clippings on boats, tanning, taxidermy, making camping equipment and other activities (Series II), 1936 (Box 142, Folder 1397)
    - Scrapbook with greeting cards (Series II), 1895-1897 (Box 143, Folder 1398-1399)
    - Scrapbook with postcards of Europe (Series II), 1905 (Box 144, Folder 1400)
    - "A Debutante Book" (Series II) (empty), circa 1907 (Box 145, Folder 1401)
    - Scrapbook with newspaper clippings on WWII (Series II), 1940s (Box 146, Folder 1402-1415)
    - Certificate appointing Gerald Murphy Second Lieutenant in the Aviation Section of the Signal Officers' Reserve Corps of the Army of the United States (Series II), 1918 April 8 (Box 147, Folder 1416)
    - Loose drawings and paintings by Patrick Murphy (Series II), Before 1937 (Box 147, Folder 1417)